Naglaa Modawi Mohammed Front-End Developer

naglaamodawi@gmail.com +249929696244

Profile

Innovative Front-end Developer with 2 years Experience, I have Developed Several Websites As Freelancer, then I worked with Team as Front-end Developer in Sudan university, and Worked as Teaching Assistant in this University Teaching the practical Side of the Web Application Course (Content of Course Server Site And Client Side and all things Related to them). Also, I Worked as Web Designer and front-end developer in Baranda Company Designing and Then Developing the Website Using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript and, jQuery.

Work Experience

Front end Developer, web designer

Baranda Company February 2021 — Present

- In this company, I am responsible for a number of tasks, the beginnings of determining the structure and design of the website, Re-transform the design into actual code, And finally, upload the website to the server
- optimizing web pages from maximum speed website
- Building reusable code for future use

Teaching assistant

Sudan University Of Science And Technology February 2020 - July 2021

Teaching the practical Side of the web application Course.

Front end developer

Sudan university of science and information technology October 2019 - October 2020

Job Description

- Convert the UI/UXdesign into organized and clear code.
- Analyzing previous pages then modifying them and correction errors in them.

Education

Bachelor / Computer System And Networks Sudan University Of Science And Technology October 2014 - November 2018

Skills

- HTML and CSS
- JavaScript
- Frameworks and Libraries
- Web Performance Optimization
- Testing and Debugging

Certification

Nafeer for Software - Capacity Building Program

National Information Center 25July - 30/July 2020

UX Design

Edraak platform June /2020

Professional Skills

Zafar Training Center 20/9 - 28/9/2020

Project Management

Edrak Platform May 2020

Business Development

Zafar Training Center

Link

Some of my previous projects

- https://naglaamodawi.github.io/My-Portfolio/
- http://baranda4xr.com
- https://naglaamodawi.github.io/HardTarget_/
- https://naglaamodawi.github.io/Tourism/index.htm